# ROSALYN LAND

roz.s.land@gmail.com

## profile

A diligent and enthusiastic full-stack developer specialising in JavaScript, with a background in foreign languages. I have a common-sense approach to problem-solving, gained through experience working in a variety of roles. I am a fast learner and always keen to pick up new skills.

### skills

Languages: JavaScript, Node.js

**Testing**: Mocha, Chai, Jest, Supertest **Back-end**: Express, Knex, PostgreSQL

Front-end: HTML5, CSS3, Adobe Illustrator and

Photoshop

Other: Git, GitHub, OOP, agile practices, CLI

Foreign languages: French, German

## education and training

#### **Deutsch Akademie, Hamburg, Germany**

German Course
APRIL 2017 - OCTOBER 2017

German course level A2 to B2 according to the CEFR

#### Hamburg School of English, Hamburg, Germany

CELTA Course

NOVEMBER 2015 - DECEMBER 2015

**Qualification**: CELTA Award. Pass

#### University of Manchester, Manchester, UK

French and Screen Studies SEPTEMBER 2011 - JUNE 2015

**Qualification**: Bachelor of Arts (Honours), Upper

second-class (2:1)

## experience

#### Northcoders Coding Bootcamp, Manchester, UK Student

JANUARY 2020 - APRIL 2020 (interrupted for lockdown period)

- Solid understanding of JavaScript full-stack development gained through daily problem-solving exercises, lectures and group work
- Implementation of agile practices, such as full test-driven-development and pair programming to deliver mini-projects to tight time-scales
- Competent use of the CLI for installing and managing software and version control

#### Goodgame Studios, Hamburg, Germany

Customer Services Representative

AUGUST 2018 - AUGUST 2019

- Liaised with customers and relayed their feedback to the development team in order to fix bugs and deploy new features in the games
- Regular 5-star ratings from customers, often with best average feedback score of the team

#### Self-employed, Hamburg, Germany

English as a Foreign Language Teacher

JANUARY 2016 - APRIL 2017

- Acquired good organisational skills through having to manage time between lesson planning, teaching and travelling
- Took initiative to create own lesson materials when they weren't available

## **DESY Housing Service, Hamburg, Germany** *Web Intern*

AUGUST 2015 - NOVEMBER 2015

- Effective use of HTML, CSS and the company's Content Management System (CMS)
- Own initiative shown by issuing survey to website users in order to make improvements